[SOUND] So
那么
there's a number of really good books on data visualization.
这里有一些非常好的 关于数据可视化的书籍
I've got a couple of them, and I've used them in putting together this course.
我自己手头有几本 在准备课程材料时用到过
I'd like to talk about some of them right now.
现在我想谈谈其中的一些书
Ed Tufte, the professor at Yale, has a number of really good books
Ed Tuffe 一名耶鲁的教授 出版过一些很好的
on visualization on the presentation of visual information.
关于如何展示视觉信息的 数据可视化书籍
These are mostly on static formats, basically constructing images and
这些书大多是关于静态格式的
being able to understand the data based on that image.
即构造一个图像 然后能基于图像去理解数据
And they're mostly focused on graphic design principles as
而且大多是集中于 图形设计的原则
opposed to the computer processing of information.
而非计算机对信息的处理
To make it more readily available for visualization.
这样就可以为数据可视化 做更充分的准备
But it's a good place to start, if you want to understand sort of the layout and
但如果想弄懂 数据可视化的整体框架
the graphic design aspects of data visualization.
以及关于图像设计的知识 这些书会是很好的开始
Also there's a really good book for scientific visualization,
还有一本很棒的书 关于科学数据的可视化
called The Visualization Handbook, and this is by Chuck Hansen and
标题是《可视化手册》 作者Chuck Hansen
Chris Johnson at the University of Utah.
和Chris Johnson 来自犹他大学
And it's mostly curated chapters written by a large number of experts
这本书由许多专家 经过严谨的考证写作而成
in scientific visualization, or the visualization of scientific data,
主要关于科学数据的可视化
or in general, data that's coordinate based,
整体而言，这些数据
based on scientific instruments or simulations.
由科学仪器产生 或者源于科学模拟
We're going to be talking about data visualization.
因为我们要讨论的是数据可视化
And so, I used as a source book a little bit this book on information
所以 作为参考 我采用了一本书中 少量有关信息可视化的内容
visualization by Stuart Card, Jock Mackinlay and Ben Schneiderman.
书的作者是Stuart Card Jock Mackinlay和Ben Schneiderman
And this is another curated collection of chapters,
这里还有一本特集书籍
the chapters are research papers.
其中的每章都是论文
The version I have came out in 2000, so it's a little bit older.
我手头的版本发表于2000年 年代有些久了
But the fundamentals really haven't changed in information visualization, and
但一些信息可视化领域基本的 原理没怎么改变过
this was a good book for me to use,
对我而言 这本书用起来非常顺手
to sort of get those fundamentals into this course.
尤其是想要在上课时 表述一些基本原理的时候
More recently, there's a good book, Information Visualization Perception for
最近出版了一本很好的书 《信息可视化：感知设计》
Design by Colin Ware at the University of New Hampshire.
作者是新罕布什尔大学 (University of Newpshire) 的Colin Ware
And, this is a book on perceptual principles applied to data visualization.
这本书主要讲解用于数据可视化 中的感知原理
So, it tells you how to lay out your data, so it can be perceived more readily.
它告诉你如何布局数据 以使它们更容易被理解
Focusing on user interface and user interaction issues.
重点在于用户界面 和交互方面的问题
And, finally, there's a really good, really recent book, Visualization Analysis
最后还有一本非常优秀的新书 《可视化分析和设计》
& Design, by Tamara Munzner at University of British Columbia.
作者是英属哥伦比亚大学 的Tamara Munzner
And it coves both scientific and information visualization, and
这本书包括了信息可视化 科学数据可视化以及
includes task analysis and other user interface details, that's quite good.
任务分析和一些交互方面的 细节知识 真的非常棒
Tamara Munzner is very well respected in the data visualization community,
Tamara Munzner在数据可视化 学界非常有声望
and this book just came out, and so it's very current, and
这本好书刚刚出版 紧跟时代潮流
a really good volume of sort of the state of the art in data visualization.
是慨括数据可视化技术 当今现状的一本好书
[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community